taiwantrade.com.tw 2018-12-27

# 

Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy identifies and describes the way Taiwan External Trade Development Council ("TAITRA", "we" or "us") uses and protects the information we collect via the websites of Taiwantrade (URL: [www.taiwantrade.com](http://www.taiwantrade.com/ "www.taiwantrade.com")) and/or iDealEZ (URL: [www.idealez.com](http://www.idealez.com/)) ( collectively the "Site") about the visitors of the Site ("Visitors"). All uses of the Site are subject to this Privacy Policy. By using the Site, you consent to our Privacy Policy set out herein.

1\. Definition

Expressions defined in the Membership Agreement entered between you and TAITRA, if any, shall (unless otherwise specifically defined herein or the context requires) have the same meanings when used in this Privacy Policy.

2\. Purpose for Information Collection

TAITRA may collect information from Visitors for purposes of providing online trading and other services of the Site, as well as marketing services and special events of TAITRA, or any purposes you agree.

3\. Classification of Personal Information

In operating the Site we may collect and process the following information about you:

  1. Information that you provide by filling in forms on our website, such as when you registered for information or make a purchase, including but not limited to your name, address, phone/fax number, email address, company profile, product catalog, trade leads, billing information, credit card numbers, expiration dates and tracking information from checks or money orders, and other information about your business;
  2. Details of your visits to the Site and the resources that you access, including but not limited to traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data;
  3. Information provided to us or others when you communicate with us or others via the Site for any reason; and
  4. Other information you provide to the Site or us.

4\. Time Period, Area, Target and Way of Use of Personal Information

TAITRA maintains a confidentiality policy on all personal information submitted by the Visitors via the Site and, for Members, TAITRA will use and/or release the submitted information in accordance with the agreement between you and TAITRA.  
Your personal information will be, subject to legal requirements, retained by TAITRA until you formally request us to erase your personal information.  
Information collected via the Site may be stored and processed in any country in which TAITRA operates, and by using the Site, you consent to any transfer of information outside of your country.  
TAITRA may provide your information to its agents, contractors or service provider which provides online payment verification or other related services (such as PayPal, HiTRUST, issuing banks, payment or amount transfer service provider(s), logistics service provider(s), certification service provider(s), eBay, and other trading platforms cooperated with TAITRA) to provide services on the Site. When Members sign up for such services, the service provider/PayPal will collect additional information (e.g., credit card number) from Members as necessary for it to provide the online payment services. On occasion, we may gather information about your computer for our services and to provide statistical information regarding the use of our website to our partners.  
We may gather information about your general internet use by using a cookie file. Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer automatically. This cookie file is stored on the hard drive of your computer as cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our website and the service that we provide to you. You may decline our use of cookies. This can be done by activating the setting on your browser which enables you to decline the cookies. Please note that should you choose to decline cookies, you may be unable to access particular parts of our website. The third party service provider of the Site may also use cookies, over which we have no control. Such cookies (if used) might be downloaded once you use the services such third party service provider offered via the Site.

5\. Access and Correction

You are entitled to make a access to and request for a review of your own personal information. Subject to the applicable laws, you may request to make duplications of, to supplement or correct, to discontinue collection, processing or use of, or to delete your own personal information,. You may log in your account of the Site to make the access and request for the review. You may also contact us to proceed with it.

6\. Consequences for Non-provision of Information

In the event you do not provide the information as requested, you may not be able to enjoy the services of the Site or achieve the purposes for which you use the Site (for instance, you may not be able to perform the online transaction on the Site).

7\. Change to Privacy Policy

Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be communicated through our posting an amended and restated Privacy Policy on the Site. Our posting the amended and restated Privacy Policy will make such new Privacy Policy immediately effective unless otherwise specified by us. You agree that all information collected via the Site (whether or not collected prior to or after the new policy became effective) will be governed by the newest Privacy Policy then in effect. If you do not agree to the new changes in our Privacy Policy, you should contact TAITRA in writing and specifically request that TAITRA return and/or destroy all copies of all or part of your personal data in TAITRA’s possession.

8\. Language

In case of any discrepancy between the traditional Chinese version of this Privacy Policy and any of its translation, the traditional Chinese version shall prevail.

9\. Questions or Suggestions

If you have any questions or suggestions, please send an email to: [e-member@taiwantrade.com](mailto:e-member@taiwantrade.com)
